Hello.
In this lecture, we are going to set up our boss character.
If we just briefly close on our engine and attached in this course lecture, I'm going to make sure
to include these files.
Just create a new folder inside Unreal Engine and call it Boss.
Head inside this folder and then drag all these images and place them inside this folder with all the
images selected.
Right click and go sprite actions and apply paper to the texture settings.
Then create a folder for each of the animations and the source sprite.
Drag each animation into its respective folder.
Next, if we create a flipbook for each of these animations, so I'll start with the attacking one or
right click and go extract Sprite.
Go to grid and make this 100 in the width and 100 and the height.
And just go extract for this sprite, just select the first five sprite and go right click, create
flipbook and call this boss attack.
Then if we go to the damage folder, we will extract these sprites.
Go to grid and change the cell width to be 100.
And if we flip for this.
And called its boss damaged.
Then if we go to the death folder, we will extract the sprite.
Change this to grid and make this 100.
Buy 100 and just go extract.
And if we slept all the sprites.
And go create flipbook and call this boss death.
Then if we go to the idle folder, extract these sprites.
Go to grid.
Trinkets.
I want to be 130 sprites.
Then if we flip for this and pull this bus, it'll.
Then finally, if we go to the salt water.
Extract these sprites.
Change this to be great.
And change the cell to be 92 and go extract.
Okay, so my project just crashed.
Make sure to go file and save all that way.
You lose your progress if your project crashes.
If we then set the first four sprites and go create a flipbook, then select the last four sprites and
go create flipbook and call this sword destroyed.
Once you've created all the animations for your boss, create any folder and call it flip books.
And put all these animation photos inside this photo.
Then create a new photo and cool this animations.
And if we just head inside here, right click and go Paper Z, select animation source, and just call
this our boss animation source.
And if we open this up.
Thank you.
Add new select new animation sequence and cool this first one boss idle and set our boss idle animation.
Then we go at new animation sequence and we'll call this our boss attack.
I will select my boss.
Attacking Animation.
I can go at new and I'll call this boss damaged and also let my boss damaged animation.
We can go add new and I'll call this boss die and I will attach my boss death animation.
Next, if we just close this.
And exit out here and create a new photo and cool this blueprints.
Head inside here and just right click and Go Blueprint class and look for Paper Z.
Select it and just call this our boss, underscore BP.
Then we can go back to our animation folder.
Right click and go paused, search, paused, animation and select the boss animation source.
And we'll just call this our boss animation blueprint.
And we can open this up.
And event on it will create a reference to the blueprint that we just made.
So our right click and look for get owning actor.
And from here we can cast to the Boss blueprint.
And then would apply this to a variable.
That way we can reference it later.
Then if we go over to the animation graph, create a new state machine.
And just connect us and do here.
If we go inside here, just drag up here and go animation state and just call this idle.
And if we hadn't thought it right click and look for Play box idle and just connect this and you here
and go compile.
That's all for now.
In the next lecture we'll set up more of the bosses blueprint.